[{"question":"What is the translation of \u6309\u65f6?","choice1":"punctual, on schedule","choice2":"responsibility","choice3":"nationality, ethnic, group","choice4":"hotel","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u529b\u6c14?","choice1":"strength","choice2":"second","choice3":"percent","choice4":"to pay","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5141\u8bb8?","choice1":"a lot of","choice2":"actor","choice3":"accurate, exact, precise","choice4":"to allow","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bcd\u8bed?","choice1":"Audience","choice2":"trash can","choice3":"Words","choice4":"famous","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5176\u4e2d?","choice1":"among (which,them.etc)","choice2":"badminton","choice3":"tiger","choice4":"toothpaste","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u590d\u6742?","choice1":"have to, must","choice2":"economic","choice3":"customer","choice4":"complex","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0f\u5b69?","choice1":"stupid","choice2":"confidence","choice3":"agent","choice4":"child","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e00\u4f1a\u513f?","choice1":"to become cooler","choice2":"accident","choice3":"utility fee","choice4":"a moment, a while, a bit","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5168\u90e8?","choice1":"humor","choice2":"to waste, to squander","choice3":"period of","choice4":"All","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9002\u5408?","choice1":"place, location, site","choice2":"Language","choice3":"Measure word for horses","choice4":"Suitable for","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d41\u884c?","choice1":"money given for children as a New Year\u2019s present","choice2":"diary","choice3":"Measure word for animals (general)","choice4":"popular","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a5\u53d7?","choice1":"even","choice2":"to accept","choice3":"to sum up","choice4":"to give up","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u60ca\u8bb6?","choice1":"at least","choice2":"amazed, to surprised, astonished","choice3":"talk","choice4":"to discuss","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u955c\u5b50?","choice1":"mirror","choice2":"full,ample,aboundant","choice3":"Simultaneously","choice4":"to receive","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8fc7\uff08to pass )?","choice1":"to pass","choice2":"future","choice3":"leaf","choice4":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a8?","choice1":"completely","choice2":"business","choice3":"those who spend their monthly income even before their next salary","choice4":"Push","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u72ec\u7acb?","choice1":"excellent, outstanding","choice2":"careless","choice3":"independent","choice4":"taste","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bc1\u660e?","choice1":"insufficient, lacking","choice2":"fax","choice3":"translation","choice4":"prove","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7701?","choice1":"province","choice2":"skin","choice3":"temporarily","choice4":"independent","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5de7\u514b\u529b?","choice1":"sock","choice2":"chocolate","choice3":"along with","choice4":"at that time, while","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bd2\u5047?","choice1":"winter vacation","choice2":"sunlight","choice3":"since","choice4":"success","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5ba2\u6ee1?","choice1":"earn","choice2":"Rush","choice3":"full","choice4":"child","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6000\u7591?","choice1":"to pull off","choice2":"to hunt","choice3":"Description","choice4":"doubt","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5783\u573e\u6876?","choice1":"didn't expect","choice2":"trash can","choice3":"broken","choice4":"reporter","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5730\u533a?","choice1":"condition, term","choice2":"area","choice3":"a short while, temporary","choice4":"feeling","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u987a\u5e8f?","choice1":"flight (measure word)","choice2":"order","choice3":"confidence","choice4":"Master's degree","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62cd?","choice1":"to pat, to clap, to swat","choice2":"difficult","choice3":"along with","choice4":"page","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u611f\u53d7?","choice1":"to tour, to visit","choice2":"to sense, to feel, a feeling, an experience","choice3":"second","choice4":"salty","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5185?","choice1":"to take off","choice2":"Inside","choice3":"lose","choice4":"horrible","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9192?","choice1":"to approach, to get close to","choice2":"wake","choice3":"Off","choice4":"Spoon","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53e5?","choice1":"Measure word for Phrases or lines of verse","choice2":"characteristic, feature, trait","choice3":"to express, to show, to say, to state, to indicate, to mean","choice4":"reduce","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5230\u65f6\u5019?","choice1":"gentle","choice2":"writer","choice3":"when the time comes, at that time","choice4":"immediate","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b66\u671f?","choice1":"in the end","choice2":"semester","choice3":"play piano","choice4":"polite, courteous, modest","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5236\u5ea6?","choice1":"father","choice2":"material","choice3":"to leave","choice4":"asystem","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u539a?","choice1":"countryside","choice2":"thick","choice3":"Quantity","choice4":"flavor","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u81f3\u5c11?","choice1":"father","choice2":"amazed, to surprised, astonished","choice3":"ability; capability","choice4":"at least","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6025\u4e8b?","choice1":"to advance, underway, in progress, to do, to carry out","choice2":"Pull","choice3":"urgent matter, pressing matter","choice4":"cash","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6210\u4e3a?","choice1":"as much as possible","choice2":"early in the morning","choice3":"qualified","choice4":"to become","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5173\u7cfb?","choice1":"Cookies","choice2":"Preview","choice3":"relation, relationship, related to","choice4":"careless","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5927\u592b?","choice1":"Yeah","choice2":"expenses,costs","choice3":"difference","choice4":"doctor","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5341\u5206?","choice1":"very","choice2":"to be poisoned, poisoning","choice3":"travel","choice4":"standard","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u591a?","choice1":"to spend","choice2":"airline company","choice3":"completely","choice4":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d6a\u8d39?","choice1":"E.g","choice2":"to waste, to squander","choice3":"according to","choice4":"bank savings","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e08\u5085?","choice1":"to remind, to call, attention to, to warn of","choice2":"belly","choice3":"master","choice4":"romantic","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bf9\u4e8e?","choice1":"sweat","choice2":"cash","choice3":"for","choice4":"rush hour,peak time","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u578b?","choice1":"section","choice2":"thick","choice3":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","choice4":"type","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6bcd\u4eb2?","choice1":"to block","choice2":"Rubber","choice3":"to cause, to lead, to give rise to","choice4":"mother","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7535\u706f?","choice1":"light","choice2":"fire","choice3":"among (which,them.etc)","choice4":"(if sb\uff09have known that......","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9053\u7406?","choice1":"to accept","choice2":"principle","choice3":"E.g","choice4":"type","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62d4\u6389?","choice1":"loan","choice2":"detailed","choice3":"to pull off","choice4":"popular","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8868\u683c?","choice1":"type","choice2":"skin","choice3":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice4":"form","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62ac?","choice1":"towel","choice2":"lift","choice3":"common","choice4":"Fiction","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e30\u5bcc?","choice1":"otherwise","choice2":"Exactly","choice3":"rich","choice4":"invention\/ to invent","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bb3\u7f9e?","choice1":"translation","choice2":"shy, embarrassed","choice3":"insufficient, lacking","choice4":"urgent matter, pressing matter","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4efb\u52a1?","choice1":"task","choice2":"the same","choice3":"to allow","choice4":"By the way","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3b\u52a8?","choice1":"to take initiative","choice2":"apartment","choice3":"lose","choice4":"success","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u786e\u5b9e?","choice1":"small inner room","choice2":"Regardless of","choice3":"indeed","choice4":"exceed","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ef7\u683c?","choice1":"to apply","choice2":"Means","choice3":"sleepy","choice4":"price","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e60\u4fd7?","choice1":"love","choice2":"custom, convention","choice3":"horrible","choice4":"pingpong","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f20\u7edf?","choice1":"grammar","choice2":"tradition","choice3":"Looks like","choice4":"rich","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u603b\u7ed3?","choice1":"to sum up","choice2":"seafood","choice3":"mineral water","choice4":"indeed","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53c2\u8003?","choice1":"Push","choice2":"to consult, to refer to, reference","choice3":"sunlight","choice4":"vegetarian","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8f6c?","choice1":"correct","choice2":"grammar","choice3":"impression","choice4":"turn","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u90ca\u533a?","choice1":"one\u2019s thoughts and feelings","choice2":"suburbs","choice3":"Cool","choice4":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f5c\u8005?","choice1":"mirror","choice2":"taste","choice3":"Hold","choice4":"Author","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8fde?","choice1":"even","choice2":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice3":"atmosphere","choice4":"fax","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u79df?","choice1":"flavor","choice2":"rent","choice3":"confidence","choice4":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u810f?","choice1":"afforested land","choice2":"dirty","choice3":"really, actually, indeed, true, honest","choice4":"Cool","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u975e\u5f97?","choice1":"and","choice2":"Roast Duck","choice3":"have to, must","choice4":"Save","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u96f6\u94b1?","choice1":"All","choice2":"countryside","choice3":"gentle","choice4":"small change","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6bdb\u5dfe?","choice1":"Author","choice2":"suburbs","choice3":"T-shirt","choice4":"towel","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5fc3\u610f?","choice1":"toothpaste","choice2":"person, character","choice3":"talk","choice4":"mind, intention, regard","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76ae\u80a4?","choice1":"impression","choice2":"to toast, to propose a toast","choice3":"skin","choice4":"environmental protection","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63d0\u9192?","choice1":"to remind, to call, attention to, to warn of","choice2":"to be particular about, stress","choice3":"dirty","choice4":"translation","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u751f\u547d?","choice1":"to approve","choice2":"agent","choice3":"to parade, march, demonstrate","choice4":"life","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8eab\u8fb9?","choice1":"at one\u2019s side, on hand","choice2":"to obtain, to get","choice3":"Candidates","choice4":"need","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6240\u6709?","choice1":"all","choice2":"By the way","choice3":"loan","choice4":"local","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5927\u5b66\u751f?","choice1":"full","choice2":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","choice3":"college student","choice4":"field","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e5f\u597d?","choice1":"pack","choice2":"be surprised","choice3":"early in the morning","choice4":"may as well","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53f0\u98ce?","choice1":"typhoon","choice2":"horrible","choice3":"boarding pass","choice4":"as much as possible","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0f\u8bf4?","choice1":"judgment","choice2":"field, side, aspect","choice3":"strength","choice4":"Fiction","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6e38\u884c?","choice1":"to parade, march, demonstrate","choice2":"relation, relationship, related to","choice3":"Yangtze","choice4":"again, once more","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f02\u5e38?","choice1":"increase","choice2":"unusal , abnormal","choice3":"customer","choice4":"doubt","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76f8\u53cd?","choice1":"to come up with, raise , propose","choice2":"not only","choice3":"GAS","choice4":"in contrast","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u57f9\u517b?","choice1":"material","choice2":"confidence","choice3":"to cultivate,to educate","choice4":"rent","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7f51\u7403?","choice1":"play piano","choice2":"tennis","choice3":"to attach importance to sth, to value","choice4":"to block","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6e29\u5ea6?","choice1":"temperature","choice2":"flight","choice3":"appear","choice4":"a lot of","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5ba2\u6c14?","choice1":"full","choice2":"polite, courteous, modest","choice3":"food","choice4":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a8\u8fdf?","choice1":"knock","choice2":"bottom","choice3":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice4":"to ride","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b89\u5168?","choice1":"form","choice2":"calm","choice3":"to change, to alter","choice4":"safe","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6570\u91cf?","choice1":"First of all","choice2":"difference","choice3":"Quantity","choice4":"one\u2019s thoughts and feelings","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u793c\u62dc\u5929?","choice1":"question","choice2":"vegetarian","choice3":"feel","choice4":"Sunday","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9ad8\u901f\u516c\u8def?","choice1":"highway","choice2":"material","choice3":"type","choice4":"sweat","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u633a?","choice1":"tableware","choice2":"gradually","choice3":"pingpong","choice4":"very","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5851\u6599\u888b?","choice1":"plastic bag","choice2":"to obtain, to get","choice3":"round trip","choice4":"By the way","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65b9\u5411?","choice1":"attitude","choice2":"direction","choice3":"to consult, to refer to, reference","choice4":"about","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u864e?","choice1":"Rubber","choice2":"citizen","choice3":"tiger","choice4":"may as well","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7cbe\u795e?","choice1":"area","choice2":"trash can","choice3":"scientist","choice4":"spirit","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7740\u51c9?","choice1":"very","choice2":"to catch a cold","choice3":"Cookies","choice4":"apartment","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51fa\u79df?","choice1":"to rent","choice2":"free","choice3":"low","choice4":"to obtain, to get","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f15\u8d77?","choice1":"experience, to experience, to go through","choice2":"proud","choice3":"work and rest","choice4":"to cause, to lead, to give rise to","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d76?","choice1":"survey","choice2":"interesting","choice3":"Rush","choice4":"how fraction being said in Chinese","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f4e?","choice1":"low","choice2":"envy, admire","choice3":"pressure","choice4":"winter vacation","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51b7\u9759?","choice1":"society","choice2":"calm","choice3":"Walking","choice4":"even","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u652f\u6301?","choice1":"we","choice2":"to support","choice3":"Knife","choice4":"the Internet","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u611f\u89c9?","choice1":"New Year","choice2":"feel","choice3":"happiness","choice4":"responsibility","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u987a\u4fbf?","choice1":"specialized, customized","choice2":"Measure wordfor long slender objects","choice3":"By the way","choice4":"handsome","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3e\u884c?","choice1":"seat","choice2":"Hold","choice3":"to change, to alter","choice4":"insufficient, lacking","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e95?","choice1":"the same","choice2":"Organized","choice3":"turn","choice4":"bottom","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f8b\u5982?","choice1":"saucer, plate, dish","choice2":"finally","choice3":"E.g","choice4":"to toast, to propose a toast","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53d1\u708e?","choice1":"to become inflamed","choice2":"full","choice3":"about","choice4":"capital","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5939?","choice1":"hold","choice2":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice3":"common","choice4":"to believe, to think","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5370\u8c61?","choice1":"for","choice2":"impression","choice3":"to believe, to think","choice4":"by","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u540e\u6094?","choice1":"punctual, on schedule","choice2":"welfare","choice3":"light","choice4":"to regret","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5440?","choice1":"Yeah","choice2":"the same","choice3":"Valentine's Day","choice4":"semester","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6e10\u6e10?","choice1":"local","choice2":"accurate, exact, precise","choice3":"gradually","choice4":"correct","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76ee\u7684\u5730?","choice1":"order","choice2":"Off","choice3":"red envelope","choice4":"destination","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e71\uff08+v\uff09?","choice1":"condition, term","choice2":"random","choice3":"spirit","choice4":"appear","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u611f\u8c22?","choice1":"thanks, grateful, thankful","choice2":"welfare","choice3":"Spoon","choice4":"to believe, to think","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e7d\u9ed8?","choice1":"to be born","choice2":"dream","choice3":"humor","choice4":"stupid","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e00\u6b21\u6027?","choice1":"to change, to alter","choice2":"one-time","choice3":"otherwise","choice4":"Baton","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c11\u65cf?","choice1":"to ride","choice2":"salty","choice3":"nationality, ethnic, group","choice4":"Make","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u957f\u57ce?","choice1":"The Great Wall","choice2":"if","choice3":"diary","choice4":"To","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5730\u9053?","choice1":"authentic, genuine, local","choice2":"All","choice3":"as, to act as, for (the sake of), to be, to do","choice4":"Young man","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65e9\u77e5\u9053?","choice1":"to celebrate","choice2":"towel","choice3":"feeling","choice4":"(if sb\uff09have known that......","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bb0\u8005?","choice1":"reporter","choice2":"fluent","choice3":"flight (measure word)","choice4":"diary","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u513f\u7ae5?","choice1":"to advance, underway, in progress, to do, to carry out","choice2":"child","choice3":"to change, to alter","choice4":"sooner or later","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e05?","choice1":"bottom","choice2":"and, also","choice3":"to leave","choice4":"handsome","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e78\u798f?","choice1":"warm","choice2":"happiness","choice3":"to ring, to sound","choice4":"Looks like","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7d20?","choice1":"advantage","choice2":"T-shirt","choice3":"vegetarian","choice4":"one-time","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u573a?","choice1":"field","choice2":"Description","choice3":"life","choice4":"to hold","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u789f\u5b50?","choice1":"toward evening, at dusk, at night fall","choice2":"flight","choice3":"full","choice4":"saucer, plate, dish","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e13\u95e8?","choice1":"Audience","choice2":"one-time","choice3":"specialized, customized","choice4":"report","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u91cd\u65b0?","choice1":"future","choice2":"thanks, grateful, thankful","choice3":"nationality, ethnic, group","choice4":"again, once more","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u822a\u7a7a\u516c\u53f8?","choice1":"doubt","choice2":"correct","choice3":"service fee, cover charge","choice4":"airline company","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6750\u6599?","choice1":"polite, courteous, modest","choice2":"material","choice3":"to pay","choice4":"buffet","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53c2\u89c2?","choice1":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice2":"to tour, to visit","choice3":"to change, to alter","choice4":"Yeah","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5171\u540c?","choice1":"to cultivate,to educate","choice2":"common","choice3":"age","choice4":"saucer, plate, dish","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f80\u5f80?","choice1":"often, frequently","choice2":"since","choice3":"have to, must","choice4":"Means","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a5\u7740?","choice1":"then","choice2":"judgment","choice3":"error","choice4":"complex","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u91ce\u5916?","choice1":"destination","choice2":"tableware","choice3":"countryside","choice4":"master","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8457\u540d?","choice1":"town","choice2":"famous","choice3":"willing","choice4":"a moment, a while, a bit","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f18\u70b9?","choice1":"to support","choice2":"by","choice3":"advantage","choice4":"at all times, any time","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6307?","choice1":"to consult, to refer to, reference","choice2":"Means","choice3":"field","choice4":"order","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c06\u6765?","choice1":"to esteem, to respect, to honor, eminent, serious","choice2":"famous","choice3":"future","choice4":"towel","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8f7b?","choice1":"light","choice2":"Measure word for horses","choice3":"to disturb, to bother, to trouble","choice4":"Inside","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9519\u8bef?","choice1":"to go to school","choice2":"usually","choice3":"error","choice4":"acid","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u904d?","choice1":"Young man","choice2":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice3":"all over","choice4":"Sunday","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7814\u7a76?","choice1":"the study","choice2":"earthquake","choice3":"school fee","choice4":"summer holiday","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u653e\u5f03?","choice1":"arm","choice2":"qualified","choice3":"to give up","choice4":"level, standard","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9884\u4e60?","choice1":"lift","choice2":"Preview","choice3":"in contrast","choice4":"question","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6392\u5217?","choice1":"gradually","choice2":"mirror","choice3":"arrangement","choice4":"usually","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7a0b\u5e8f?","choice1":"procedure","choice2":"badminton","choice3":"leaf","choice4":"proud, pride, arrogance","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7279\u5f81?","choice1":"local","choice2":"characteristic, feature, trait","choice3":"WC","choice4":"print","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ea2\u5305?","choice1":"as much as possible","choice2":"red envelope","choice3":"to congratulate","choice4":"if","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7b11\u8bdd?","choice1":"vacation","choice2":"early in the month","choice3":"joke","choice4":"even if","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7406\u89e3?","choice1":"to understand, to comprehend","choice2":"GAS","choice3":"to discuss","choice4":"actor","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4fe1\u606f?","choice1":"to promote, to sell","choice2":"to joke","choice3":"invention\/ to invent","choice4":"information","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6ee1?","choice1":"Words","choice2":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice3":"full","choice4":"to recycle","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e76\u4e14?","choice1":"sunlight","choice2":"and, also","choice3":"afforested land","choice4":"tableware","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a8\u9500?","choice1":"criticism","choice2":"accident","choice3":"opposite","choice4":"to promote, to sell","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d5e\u6210?","choice1":"Articles","choice2":"to approve","choice3":"parking space","choice4":"asystem","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5224\u65ad?","choice1":"direction","choice2":"judgment","choice3":"Rubber","choice4":"red envelope","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56fa\u7136?","choice1":"by","choice2":"very","choice3":"according to","choice4":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u889c\u5b50?","choice1":"sock","choice2":"to come up with, raise , propose","choice3":"T-shirt","choice4":"From","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6253\u6270?","choice1":"grammar","choice2":"bottom","choice3":"to disturb, to bother, to trouble","choice4":"guide","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e92\u8054\u7f51?","choice1":"countryside","choice2":"those who spend their monthly income even before their next salary","choice3":"the Internet","choice4":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8054\u7cfb?","choice1":"spirit","choice2":"hair","choice3":"to contact","choice4":"Only","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6279\u8bc4?","choice1":"difference","choice2":"specialized, customized","choice3":"criticism","choice4":"often, frequently","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5835\u585e?","choice1":"First of all","choice2":"to block","choice3":"Roast Duck","choice4":"to oppose","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u80f3\u818a?","choice1":"arm","choice2":"among (which,them.etc)","choice3":"round trip","choice4":"bitter","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u61d2?","choice1":"and, also","choice2":"punctual, on schedule","choice3":"cloud","choice4":"lazy","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5931\u671b?","choice1":"Measure wordfor long slender objects","choice2":"disappoint","choice3":"amazed, to surprised, astonished","choice4":"Off","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7edd\u5bf9?","choice1":"household, family","choice2":"absolutely","choice3":"temperature","choice4":"punctual, on schedule","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ffb\u8bd1?","choice1":"repair","choice2":"to contact","choice3":"leaf","choice4":"translation","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e00\u5927\u65e9?","choice1":"to move emotionally, to excite","choice2":"but","choice3":"early in the morning","choice4":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53f6\u5b50?","choice1":"to go to school","choice2":"leaf","choice3":"free","choice4":"painter","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u987a\u5229?","choice1":"Author","choice2":"smooth going,smoothly","choice3":"Spoon","choice4":"error","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c14\u6c1b?","choice1":"toothpaste","choice2":"atmosphere","choice3":"Preview","choice4":"T-shirt","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u533a\u522b?","choice1":"society","choice2":"acid","choice3":"difference","choice4":"popular","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d77\u6d0b?","choice1":"ocean","choice2":"smooth going,smoothly","choice3":"survey","choice4":"lift","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6bdb?","choice1":"hair","choice2":"difficult","choice3":"procedure","choice4":"proud","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d23\u4efb?","choice1":"child","choice2":"to be sure, must","choice3":"common","choice4":"responsibility","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d17\u8863\u673a?","choice1":"washing machine","choice2":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice3":"punctual, on schedule","choice4":"completely","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6001\u5ea6?","choice1":"indeed","choice2":"reason","choice3":"attitude","choice4":"bank savings","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9910\u76d2?","choice1":"college student","choice2":"small change","choice3":"meal box","choice4":"diary","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3b\u4eba?","choice1":"dream","choice2":"landing","choice3":"urgent matter, pressing matter","choice4":"master, host, owner","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4eba\u7269?","choice1":"annoying","choice2":"person, character","choice3":"measure word for document, paper, portion, part","choice4":"saucer, plate, dish","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f20\u771f?","choice1":"lawyer","choice2":"beautiful","choice3":"both","choice4":"fax","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bb2\u7a76?","choice1":"to be particular about, stress","choice2":"regardless","choice3":"specialized, customized","choice4":"payment","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u52fa\u5b50?","choice1":"Spoon","choice2":"number","choice3":"to force (sb to do sth","choice4":"taste","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f97\u610f?","choice1":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","choice2":"proud","choice3":"Yeah","choice4":"to approve","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d37\u6b3e?","choice1":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice2":"loan","choice3":"future","choice4":"speed, pace","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u666e\u901a?","choice1":"to do, to make","choice2":"common","choice3":"feast, banquet","choice4":"to contact","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bcc?","choice1":"to respect, to revere","choice2":"form","choice3":"rich","choice4":"chocolate","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8ddd\u79bb?","choice1":"type","choice2":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","choice3":"distance","choice4":"welfare","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c1d?","choice1":"very","choice2":"Yeah","choice3":"at the minimum, at the very least","choice4":"taste","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6536\u62fe?","choice1":"to take off","choice2":"full","choice3":"Sunday","choice4":"pack","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6708\u5149\u65cf?","choice1":"one way, one path","choice2":"those who spend their monthly income even before their next salary","choice3":"field","choice4":"flight (measure word)","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a8\u51fa?","choice1":"trash can","choice2":"distance","choice3":"small change","choice4":"to push out, to release","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u795d\u8d3a?","choice1":"responsibility","choice2":"sure","choice3":"to congratulate","choice4":"Knife","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u68a8?","choice1":"and, also","choice2":"pear","choice3":"to approve","choice4":"full","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5145\u5206?","choice1":"full,ample,aboundant","choice2":"to miss appointment","choice3":"actor","choice4":"temporarily","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u672c\u6765?","choice1":"originally","choice2":"Measure word for animals (general)","choice3":"by","choice4":"E.g","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7f8e\u4e3d?","choice1":"ocean","choice2":"beautiful","choice3":"bedroom","choice4":"balcony","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u770b\u6cd5?","choice1":"opinion","choice2":"stupid","choice3":"life","choice4":"as, to act as, for (the sake of), to be, to do","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u82b1?","choice1":"prove","choice2":"level, standard","choice3":"First of all","choice4":"to spend","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53d6?","choice1":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice2":"Candidates","choice3":"T-shirt","choice4":"take","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6709\u8da3?","choice1":"interesting","choice2":"Preview","choice3":"by","choice4":"all","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u786e\u8ba4?","choice1":"red envelope","choice2":"to confirm","choice3":"habit,get used to","choice4":"versus","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u751f\u610f?","choice1":"to play the host, to host sb","choice2":"at all times, any time","choice3":"regardless","choice4":"business","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4efd?","choice1":"urgent matter, pressing matter","choice2":"very","choice3":"at all times, any time","choice4":"measure word for document, paper, portion, part","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63a5\u8fd1?","choice1":"again, once more","choice2":"to approach, to get close to","choice3":"vacation","choice4":"suburbs","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u540d\u7247?","choice1":"rich","choice2":"business cards","choice3":"to waste, to squander","choice4":"the same","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of T\u6064\u886b?","choice1":"since","choice2":"T-shirt","choice3":"earthquake","choice4":"WC","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ed3\u5a5a?","choice1":"arrangement","choice2":"report","choice3":"to separate","choice4":"to get married","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u590d\u5370?","choice1":"winter vacation","choice2":"doctor","choice3":"copy","choice4":"willing","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53ca\u65f6?","choice1":"but","choice2":"to be born","choice3":"immediate","choice4":"beautiful","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9996\u90fd?","choice1":"to praise, to commend","choice2":"capital","choice3":"to receive","choice4":"mention","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0a\u5b66?","choice1":"to go to school","choice2":"to be particular about, stress","choice3":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","choice4":"economic","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u68a6?","choice1":"hair","choice2":"play piano","choice3":"dream","choice4":"take","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e91?","choice1":"cloud","choice2":"be surprised","choice3":"to become cooler","choice4":"to parade, march, demonstrate","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5ba2\u5385?","choice1":"living room","choice2":"characteristic, feature, trait","choice3":"fee, cost","choice4":"along with","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u79bb\u5f00?","choice1":"invention\/ to invent","choice2":"tennis","choice3":"to leave","choice4":"According to","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u666f\u8272?","choice1":"to separate","choice2":"proud","choice3":"handsome","choice4":"view","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e74\u7eaa?","choice1":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice2":"translation","choice3":"life","choice4":"age","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6765\u5f97\u53ca?","choice1":"It's too late","choice2":"Only","choice3":"to play the host, to host sb","choice4":"Make","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5473\u9053?","choice1":"taste","choice2":"disaster","choice3":"to represent","choice4":"to accept","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e73\u65f6?","choice1":"to esteem, to respect, to honor, eminent, serious","choice2":"usually","choice3":"to be sure, must","choice4":"Words","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ed8\u6b3e?","choice1":"common","choice2":"Language","choice3":"bitter","choice4":"payment","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u957f\u671f?","choice1":"long term,","choice2":"sock","choice3":"handsome","choice4":"Baton","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5426\u5219?","choice1":"period of","choice2":"to miss appointment","choice3":"otherwise","choice4":"bun","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u706b?","choice1":"household, family","choice2":"typhoon","choice3":"fire","choice4":"to give up","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u670d\u52a1\u8d39?","choice1":"explanation, to explain","choice2":"mineral water","choice3":"service fee, cover charge","choice4":"to confirm","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u79d2?","choice1":"second","choice2":"experience, to experience, to go through","choice3":"grammar","choice4":"earn","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4fe1\u7528\u5361?","choice1":"tiger","choice2":"full","choice3":"Measure wordfor long slender objects","choice4":"credit card","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c34\u5e73?","choice1":"level, standard","choice2":"to congratulate","choice3":"careful","choice4":"may as well","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c34\u7535\u8d39?","choice1":"to wedge between, to clip, to press from either side","choice2":"utility fee","choice3":"among (which,them.etc)","choice4":"joke","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d41\u5229?","choice1":"advantage","choice2":"fluent","choice3":"to contact","choice4":"Measure word for animals (general)","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u52a8\u4f5c?","choice1":"life","choice2":"stupid","choice3":"action","choice4":"advantage","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7236\u4eb2?","choice1":"absolutely","choice2":"father","choice3":"results, conclusion, as a result, in the end","choice4":"handsome","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5206\u4e4b?","choice1":"absolutely","choice2":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice3":"afforested land","choice4":"feel","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6839\uff08Measure word)?","choice1":"be surprised","choice2":"meal box","choice3":"Measure wordfor long slender objects","choice4":"to block","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u60c5\u4eba\u8282?","choice1":"meal box","choice2":"Valentine's Day","choice3":"lawyer","choice4":"to be poisoned, poisoning","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7855\u58eb?","choice1":"Master's degree","choice2":"often, frequently","choice3":"agent","choice4":"Haircut","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5047?","choice1":"citizen","choice2":"vacation","choice3":"to toast, to propose a toast","choice4":"disaster","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u884c?","choice1":"cherish","choice2":"Row","choice3":"plant","choice4":"landing","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bb8\u591a?","choice1":"all","choice2":"a lot of","choice3":"indeed","choice4":"full,ample,aboundant","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56fd\u9645?","choice1":"even","choice2":"international","choice3":"copy","choice4":"full","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76f8\u540c?","choice1":"the same","choice2":"and, also","choice3":"reason","choice4":"to push out, to release","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f39\u94a2\u7434?","choice1":"joke","choice2":"college student","choice3":"play piano","choice4":"Country of Citizenship","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0e?","choice1":"have to, must","choice2":"highway","choice3":"versus","choice4":"a lot of","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6682\u65f6?","choice1":"sock","choice2":"The Great Wall","choice3":"Rush","choice4":"temporarily","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c61\u67d3?","choice1":"Baton","choice2":"expenses,costs","choice3":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","choice4":"Pollution","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e52\u4e53\u7403?","choice1":"pingpong","choice2":"strength","choice3":"master, host, owner","choice4":"then","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7b28?","choice1":"acid","choice2":"stupid","choice3":"due to","choice4":"lazy","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bb6\u5177?","choice1":"furniture","choice2":"not only\/have to","choice3":"Make","choice4":"rich","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8282\u65e5?","choice1":"to express, expression, facial expression","choice2":"Fiction","choice3":"Articles","choice4":"festival","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5165\u53e3?","choice1":"leaf","choice2":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","choice3":"Entrance","choice4":"area","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u641e?","choice1":"to be particular about, stress","choice2":"reporter","choice3":"to do, to make","choice4":"saucer, plate, dish","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51c9\u5feb?","choice1":"diary","choice2":"Cool","choice3":"environmental protection","choice4":"town","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u89c4\u5f8b?","choice1":"college student","choice2":"feel","choice3":"regular pattern","choice4":"need","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u718a\u732b?","choice1":"panda","choice2":"difference","choice3":"repair","choice4":"utility fee","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6027\u522b?","choice1":"Sunday","choice2":"gender","choice3":"to compensate","choice4":"have to, must","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u591c\u732b\u5b50?","choice1":"a person who goes to bed late,night owl","choice2":"reason","choice3":"town","choice4":"Sunday","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4fee\u7406?","choice1":"repair","choice2":"politeness","choice3":"question","choice4":"be surprised","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u98df\u7269?","choice1":"food","choice2":"child","choice3":"joke","choice4":"rich","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c24\u5176?","choice1":"about","choice2":"especially","choice3":"economic","choice4":"It's too late","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3e?","choice1":"the study","choice2":"for","choice3":"fax","choice4":"Give","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u96be\u9053?","choice1":"immediate","choice2":"Is it","choice3":"custom, convention","choice4":"unusal , abnormal","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62b1?","choice1":"condition, term","choice2":"hold","choice3":"gender","choice4":"advantage","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56de\u6536?","choice1":"Author","choice2":"pocket money","choice3":"to esteem, to respect, to honor, eminent, serious","choice4":"to recycle","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u538b\u529b?","choice1":"relatives","choice2":"pressure","choice3":"reduce","choice4":"a short while, temporary","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d54?","choice1":"dream","choice2":"vacation","choice3":"to compensate","choice4":"sooner or later","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6e29\u67d4?","choice1":"taste","choice2":"to take off","choice3":"gentle","choice4":"all","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u793e\u4f1a?","choice1":"at least","choice2":"absolutely","choice3":"really, actually, indeed, true, honest","choice4":"society","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56fd\u7c4d?","choice1":"custom, convention","choice2":"to apply","choice3":"Country of Citizenship","choice4":"section","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53ea\u597d?","choice1":"Suitable for","choice2":"Only","choice3":"to disturb, to bother, to trouble","choice4":"advantage","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bb6\u5ead?","choice1":"very","choice2":"hospitable, friendly, good at hosting others","choice3":"salty","choice4":"household, family","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u81ea\u52a9\u9910?","choice1":"environmental protection","choice2":"buffet","choice3":"smooth going,smoothly","choice4":"light","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u79d1\u5b66\uff08\u5bb6\uff09?","choice1":"diary","choice2":"Save","choice3":"scientist","choice4":"to attach importance to sth, to value","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6311\u9009?","choice1":"to pick","choice2":"a moment, a while, a bit","choice3":"loan","choice4":"grammar","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5305\u5b50?","choice1":"lazy","choice2":"to pull off","choice3":"bun","choice4":"to play the host, to host sb","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51fa\u73b0?","choice1":"WC","choice2":"appear","choice3":"play piano","choice4":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e58\u5750?","choice1":"Young man","choice2":"sock","choice3":"earthquake","choice4":"to ride","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u83b7\u5f97?","choice1":"to obtain, to get","choice2":"salty","choice3":"to approve","choice4":"reason","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62bd\u70df?","choice1":"area","choice2":"lift","choice3":"to change, to alter","choice4":"smokes","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7740\u540d?","choice1":"famous","choice2":"toward evening, at dusk, at night fall","choice3":"disaster","choice4":"belly","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u81ea\u4fe1?","choice1":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice2":"belly","choice3":"confidence","choice4":"Pollution","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3a?","choice1":"as, to act as, for (the sake of), to be, to do","choice2":"to waste, to squander","choice3":"It","choice4":"customer","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b8b\u671d?","choice1":"relatives","choice2":"Song dynasty","choice3":"pocket money","choice4":"polite, courteous, modest","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u89e3\u91ca?","choice1":"anyway","choice2":"explanation, to explain","choice3":"survey","choice4":"Close","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bf4\u660e?","choice1":"By the way","choice2":"fax","choice3":"painter","choice4":"Description","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5408\u683c?","choice1":"very","choice2":"qualified","choice3":"vegetarian","choice4":"to approach, to get close to","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4eba\u6c11?","choice1":"street","choice2":"citizen","choice3":"to pay","choice4":"Measure word for horses","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9152\u5e2d?","choice1":"action","choice2":"feast, banquet","choice3":"town","choice4":"should","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u597d\u5ba2?","choice1":"grammar","choice2":"a lot of","choice3":"hospitable, friendly, good at hosting others","choice4":"happiness","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8be6\u7ec6?","choice1":"Young man","choice2":"school fee","choice3":"happiness","choice4":"detailed","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7167?","choice1":"According to","choice2":"all","choice3":"lazy","choice4":"tiger","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8282?","choice1":"joy, fun","choice2":"happiness","choice3":"Festival","choice4":"to pull off","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56db\u5ddd?","choice1":"take","choice2":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","choice3":"the Internet","choice4":"winter vacation","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5403\u60ca?","choice1":"be surprised","choice2":"fluent","choice3":"economic","choice4":"countryside","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u751a\u81f3?","choice1":"even","choice2":"sugar","choice3":"happiness","choice4":"to promote, to sell","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6559\u6388?","choice1":"at that time, while","choice2":"to discuss","choice3":"professor","choice4":"fee, cost","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6210\u529f?","choice1":"to apply","choice2":"food","choice3":"success","choice4":"both","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5546\u91cf?","choice1":"to be sure, must","choice2":"absolutely","choice3":"responsibility","choice4":"to discuss","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56f0\u96be?","choice1":"Exactly","choice2":"difficult","choice3":"bedroom","choice4":"translation","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e94\u8058?","choice1":"Candidates","choice2":"reduce","choice3":"invention\/ to invent","choice4":"often, frequently","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5411\u5bfc?","choice1":"guide","choice2":"confidence","choice3":"to miss appointment","choice4":"currently","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6253\u730e?","choice1":"to hunt","choice2":"translation","choice3":"by","choice4":"for","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9875?","choice1":"Words","choice2":"page","choice3":"hold","choice4":"fill in the blank","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u968f\u7740?","choice1":"school fee","choice2":"to enjoy, to appreciate","choice3":"politeness","choice4":"along with","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5339?","choice1":"Measure word for horses","choice2":"grape","choice3":"cloud","choice4":"rush hour,peak time","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9996\u5148?","choice1":"to become cooler","choice2":"humor","choice3":"First of all","choice4":"Cookies","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62c9?","choice1":"landing","choice2":"to leave (a message), to remain, to retain, to stay","choice3":"Pull","choice4":"even","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d77\u9c9c?","choice1":"seafood","choice2":"Push","choice3":"show","choice4":"loan","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e00\u90e8\u5206?","choice1":"according to","choice2":"part of it","choice3":"order","choice4":"again, once more","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7559?","choice1":"bun","choice2":"temper","choice3":"safe","choice4":"to leave (a message), to remain, to retain, to stay","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5931\u7ea6?","choice1":"atmosphere","choice2":"to miss appointment","choice3":"lift","choice4":"may as well","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6807\u51c6?","choice1":"cloud","choice2":"pingpong","choice3":"to regret","choice4":"standard","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7259\u818f?","choice1":"local","choice2":"to leave","choice3":"toothpaste","choice4":"stupid","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u96f6\u82b1\u94b1?","choice1":"pocket money","choice2":"to understand, to comprehend","choice3":"to sense, to feel, a feeling, an experience","choice4":"to play the host, to host sb","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8857?","choice1":"action","choice2":"fire","choice3":"direction","choice4":"street","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6c57?","choice1":"Exactly","choice2":"sweat","choice3":"to leave","choice4":"specialized, customized","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u767e\u5206\u4e4b?","choice1":"percent","choice2":"Busy","choice3":"to oppose","choice4":"to take off","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d5a?","choice1":"to contact","choice2":"thanks, grateful, thankful","choice3":"earn","choice4":"Pollution","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u516c\u5bd3?","choice1":"may as well","choice2":"pack","choice3":"sunlight","choice4":"apartment","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u70e6\u4eba?","choice1":"Focus","choice2":"especially","choice3":"(if sb\uff09have known that......","choice4":"annoying","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u88c5?","choice1":"GAS","choice2":"money given for children as a New Year\u2019s present","choice3":"to hold","choice4":"future","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ecf\u5386?","choice1":"experience, to experience, to go through","choice2":"need","choice3":"earn","choice4":"life","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65c5\u884c?","choice1":"service fee, cover charge","choice2":"travel","choice3":"to recycle","choice4":"Yangtze","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u68d2?","choice1":"Means","choice2":"balcony","choice3":"Baton","choice4":"to hunt","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u968f\u65f6?","choice1":"horrible","choice2":"at all times, any time","choice3":"stupid","choice4":"tradition","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u533b\u7597?","choice1":"tennis","choice2":"medical","choice3":"to leave (a message), to remain, to retain, to stay","choice4":"Walking","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5206\u79bb?","choice1":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","choice2":"Rush","choice3":"random","choice4":"to separate","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6ca1\u60f3\u5230?","choice1":"famous","choice2":"didn't expect","choice3":"to promote, to sell","choice4":"Pollution","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53d7\u5230?","choice1":"regular pattern","choice2":"love","choice3":"to receive","choice4":"feel","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7231\u60c5?","choice1":"to miss appointment","choice2":"love","choice3":"mind, intention, regard","choice4":"if","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u603b\u7b97?","choice1":"countryside","choice2":"finally","choice3":"customer","choice4":"It's too late","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bed\u6cd5?","choice1":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","choice2":"grammar","choice3":"didn't expect","choice4":"to pass","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76ee\u524d?","choice1":"currently","choice2":"proud, pride, arrogance","choice3":"broken","choice4":"to allow","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6563\u6b65?","choice1":"rush hour,peak time","choice2":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","choice3":"Walking","choice4":"travel","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b58\u6b3e?","choice1":"saucer, plate, dish","choice2":"completely","choice3":"middle age person","choice4":"bank savings","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5fcd\u8010?","choice1":"to bear with, endure","choice2":"environmental protection","choice3":"relatives","choice4":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u662f\u5426?","choice1":"whether","choice2":"seat","choice3":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice4":"regular pattern","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6559\u80b2?","choice1":"sooner or later","choice2":"to understand, to comprehend","choice3":"to educate","choice4":"plastic bag","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5730\u9707?","choice1":"print","choice2":"qualified","choice3":"To","choice4":"earthquake","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5200?","choice1":"to contact","choice2":"currently","choice3":"Knife","choice4":"careless","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u73cd\u60dc?","choice1":"sunlight","choice2":"festival","choice3":"cherish","choice4":"immediate","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5355\u7a0b?","choice1":"Suitable for","choice2":"to be born","choice3":"one way, one path","choice4":"task","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6fc0\u52a8?","choice1":"to leave (a message), to remain, to retain, to stay","choice2":"proud, pride, arrogance","choice3":"to move emotionally, to excite","choice4":"From","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9178?","choice1":"acid","choice2":"ancient time","choice3":"again, once more","choice4":"free","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u809a\u5b50?","choice1":"travel","choice2":"belly","choice3":"section","choice4":"especially","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6309\u7167?","choice1":"to catch a cold","choice2":"according to","choice3":"to force (sb to do sth","choice4":"thick","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65b9\u9762?","choice1":"nationality, ethnic, group","choice2":"to go to school","choice3":"free","choice4":"field, side, aspect","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6700\u597d?","choice1":"the best","choice2":"living room","choice3":"willing","choice4":"toward evening, at dusk, at night fall","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f8b\u5e08?","choice1":"lawyer","choice2":"very","choice3":"measure word for document, paper, portion, part","choice4":"credit card","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u793c\u8c8c?","choice1":"rich","choice2":"smokes","choice3":"politeness","choice4":"to hunt","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7531?","choice1":"to sum up","choice2":"by","choice3":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","choice4":"to come up with, raise , propose","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b9e\u5728?","choice1":"Fiction","choice2":"really, actually, indeed, true, honest","choice3":"towel","choice4":"buffet","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53cd\u6b63?","choice1":"love","choice2":"to change, to alter","choice3":"popular","choice4":"anyway","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ee5\u4e3a?","choice1":"to believe, to think","choice2":"to go to school","choice3":"Busy","choice4":"gradually","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f18\u52bf?","choice1":"results, conclusion, as a result, in the end","choice2":"advantage","choice3":"to promote, to sell","choice4":"warm","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u505a\u4e1c?","choice1":"not only\/have to","choice2":"very","choice3":"have to, must","choice4":"to play the host, to host sb","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f4d\u7f6e?","choice1":"Off","choice2":"to praise, to commend","choice3":"taste","choice4":"place, location, site","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5360\u7ebf?","choice1":"Busy","choice2":"thanks, grateful, thankful","choice3":"at least","choice4":"thick","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u80fd\u529b?","choice1":"ability; capability","choice2":"WC","choice3":"to support","choice4":"to compensate","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u80af?","choice1":"summer holiday","choice2":"have to, must","choice3":"willing","choice4":"to become inflamed","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9633\u5149?","choice1":"to esteem, to respect, to honor, eminent, serious","choice2":"full,ample,aboundant","choice3":"sunlight","choice4":"criticism","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u91cd\u89c6?","choice1":"page","choice2":"Quantity","choice3":"atmosphere","choice4":"to attach importance to sth, to value","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0d\u5f97\u4e0d?","choice1":"bedroom","choice2":"to congratulate","choice3":"unusal , abnormal","choice4":"not only\/have to","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5927\u7ea6?","choice1":"Exactly","choice2":"about","choice3":"field, side, aspect","choice4":"sunlight","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6bd4\u5982?","choice1":"ocean","choice2":"such as","choice3":"mirror","choice4":"tiger","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9a6c?","choice1":"Save","choice2":"horse","choice3":"second","choice4":"to praise, to commend","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5230\u5e95?","choice1":"success","choice2":"person, character","choice3":"to regret","choice4":"in the end","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u903c?","choice1":"to force (sb to do sth","choice2":"popular","choice3":"then","choice4":"to confirm","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u70e4\u9e2d?","choice1":"independent","choice2":"Roast Duck","choice3":"thick","choice4":"bedroom","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u77ff\u6cc9\u6c34?","choice1":"smokes","choice2":"mineral water","choice3":"temporarily","choice4":"guide","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ee3\u8868?","choice1":"order","choice2":"to represent","choice3":"according to","choice4":"It","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u98ce\u5473?","choice1":"flavor","choice2":"to recycle","choice3":"towel","choice4":"Organized","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f5c\u606f?","choice1":"small inner room","choice2":"work and rest","choice3":"pack","choice4":"due to","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u56f0?","choice1":"unusal , abnormal","choice2":"sleepy","choice3":"apartment","choice4":"welfare","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5367\u5ba4?","choice1":"bedroom","choice2":"the Internet","choice3":"bridge","choice4":"loan","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u964d\u843d?","choice1":"annual leave","choice2":"landing","choice3":"mention","choice4":"feast, banquet","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8fdb\u884c?","choice1":"period of","choice2":"school fee","choice3":"authentic, genuine, local","choice4":"to advance, underway, in progress, to do, to carry out","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u89c2\u4f17?","choice1":"Audience","choice2":"airline company","choice3":"page","choice4":"to get married","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u901f\u5ea6?","choice1":"absolutely","choice2":"life","choice3":"hold","choice4":"speed, pace","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8c03\u67e5?","choice1":"page","choice2":"to give up","choice3":"survey","choice4":"to leave","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u997c\u5e72?","choice1":"be worth","choice2":"Cookies","choice3":"action","choice4":"have to, must","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u54b8?","choice1":"salty","choice2":"ocean","choice3":"full","choice4":"to compensate","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0d\u8db3?","choice1":"insufficient, lacking","choice2":"to educate","choice3":"plastic bag","choice4":"Author","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u679c\u6c41?","choice1":"credit card","choice2":"fruit juice","choice3":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","choice4":"to adapt; to accommodate","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7fbd\u6bdb\u7403?","choice1":"work and rest","choice2":"badminton","choice3":"detailed","choice4":"towel","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7cd6?","choice1":"sugar","choice2":"capital","choice3":"common","choice4":"to take initiative","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0d\u7ba1?","choice1":"Regardless of","choice2":"Quantity","choice3":"place, location, site","choice4":"Yeah","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u592b\u59bb?","choice1":"full","choice2":"couple","choice3":"tableware","choice4":"to discuss","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u611f\u89e6?","choice1":"should","choice2":"immediate","choice3":"one\u2019s thoughts and feelings","choice4":"throat","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6f14\u51fa?","choice1":"chocolate","choice2":"otherwise","choice3":"show","choice4":"Song dynasty","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9898?","choice1":"invention\/ to invent","choice2":"to rent","choice3":"to leave","choice4":"question","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u611f\u60c5?","choice1":"salty","choice2":"feeling","choice3":"a lot of","choice4":"correct","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7531\u4e8e?","choice1":"panda","choice2":"lift","choice3":"material","choice4":"due to","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9152\u5e97?","choice1":"percent","choice2":"report","choice3":"earthquake","choice4":"hotel","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e4b\u95f4?","choice1":"between","choice2":"rich","choice3":"as long as","choice4":"distance","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u610f\u5916?","choice1":"flavor","choice2":"accident","choice3":"The Great Wall","choice4":"to disturb, to bother, to trouble","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6b7b?","choice1":"prove","choice2":"to take off","choice3":"dead","choice4":"early in the morning","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6a61\u76ae?","choice1":"interesting","choice2":"action","choice3":"to take initiative","choice4":"Rubber","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bf9\u8c61?","choice1":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","choice2":"form","choice3":"usually","choice4":"seafood","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f53\u5730?","choice1":"town","choice2":"life","choice3":"local","choice4":"as much as possible","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4eab\u53d7?","choice1":"to enjoy, to appreciate","choice2":"regardless","choice3":"area","choice4":"Song dynasty","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u964d\u6e29?","choice1":"to become cooler","choice2":"even if","choice3":"percent","choice4":"one-time","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8c08?","choice1":"to be sure, must","choice2":"talk","choice3":"full","choice4":"environmental protection","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c3d\u91cf?","choice1":"to become","choice2":"very","choice3":"as much as possible","choice4":"province","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6b63\u597d?","choice1":"Exactly","choice2":"such as","choice3":"finally","choice4":"be surprised","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6491?","choice1":"gentle","choice2":"full","choice3":"Means","choice4":"saucer, plate, dish","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bda\u5b9e?","choice1":"area","choice2":"professor","choice3":"attitude","choice4":"honesty","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8bed\u8a00?","choice1":"type","choice2":"Language","choice3":"about","choice4":"It's too late","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8be5?","choice1":"should","choice2":"actor","choice3":"Language","choice4":"as long as","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4fe1\u5fc3?","choice1":"to allow","choice2":"Sunday","choice3":"mother","choice4":"confidence","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5395\u6240?","choice1":"excellent, outstanding","choice2":"payment","choice3":"about","choice4":"WC","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u707e\u5bb3?","choice1":"ability; capability","choice2":"to celebrate","choice3":"according to","choice4":"disaster","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u690d\u7269?","choice1":"plant","choice2":"to spend","choice3":"utility fee","choice4":"smooth going,smoothly","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d85\u8fc7?","choice1":"to express, to show, to say, to state, to indicate, to mean","choice2":"Regardless of","choice3":"both","choice4":"exceed","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53d7\u4e0d\u4e86?","choice1":"accident","choice2":"earthquake","choice3":"complex","choice4":"can't stand, to be unable to stand sth.","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6765\u81ea?","choice1":"From","choice2":"place, location, site","choice3":"independent","choice4":"nationality, ethnic, group","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ed4\u7ec6?","choice1":"careful","choice2":"Give","choice3":"to recycle","choice4":"judgment","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53cd\u5bf9?","choice1":"badminton","choice2":"to oppose","choice3":"indeed","choice4":"judgment","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63d0\u51fa?","choice1":"seat","choice2":"even","choice3":"to come up with, raise , propose","choice4":"agent","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53ea\u8981?","choice1":"shy, embarrassed","choice2":"as long as","choice3":"one-time","choice4":"sweat","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d77\u98de?","choice1":"to represent","choice2":"to take off","choice3":"mineral water","choice4":"flight","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u653e\u6691\u5047?","choice1":"disaster","choice2":"not only","choice3":"advantage","choice4":"summer holiday","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9700\u8981?","choice1":"to play the host, to host sb","choice2":"the Internet","choice3":"need","choice4":"thick","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ed3\u679c?","choice1":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice2":"Entrance","choice3":"anyway","choice4":"results, conclusion, as a result, in the end","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9ad8\u5cf0\u65f6\u671f?","choice1":"the same","choice2":"red envelope","choice3":"rush hour,peak time","choice4":"opinion","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u800c?","choice1":"Master's degree","choice2":"fluent","choice3":"economic","choice4":"and","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e2d\u5e74\u4eba?","choice1":"correct","choice2":"middle age person","choice3":"tableware","choice4":"between","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d77\u7801?","choice1":"a lot of","choice2":"First of all","choice3":"reason","choice4":"at the minimum, at the very least","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9a84\u50b2?","choice1":"proud, pride, arrogance","choice2":"absolutely","choice3":"level, standard","choice4":"bridge","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5e74\u5047?","choice1":"hospitable, friendly, good at hosting others","choice2":"lazy","choice3":"annual leave","choice4":"Yeah","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53f7\u7801?","choice1":"earn","choice2":"random","choice3":"number","choice4":"to become","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u666e\u901a\u8bdd?","choice1":"Mandarin","choice2":"travel","choice3":"opinion","choice4":"painter","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u586b\u7a7a?","choice1":"pack","choice2":"nationality, ethnic, group","choice3":"and","choice4":"fill in the blank","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5957\u95f4?","choice1":"Organized","choice2":"increase","choice3":"small inner room","choice4":"to tour, to visit","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u751f\u6d3b?","choice1":"loan","choice2":"life","choice3":"bottom","choice4":"free","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u82e6?","choice1":"arrangement","choice2":"relatives","choice3":"bitter","choice4":"to take initiative","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ee5?","choice1":"To","choice2":"full","choice3":"cash","choice4":"to advance, underway, in progress, to do, to carry out","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7eff\u5730?","choice1":"afforested land","choice2":"warm","choice3":"indeed","choice4":"apartment","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u91cd\u70b9?","choice1":"punctual, on schedule","choice2":"Focus","choice3":"Fiction","choice4":"thick","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5343\u4e07?","choice1":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice2":"to be sure, must","choice3":"airline company","choice4":"Yangtze","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8fc7\uff08to celebrate\uff09?","choice1":"warm","choice2":"joy, fun","choice3":"small inner room","choice4":"to celebrate","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b66\u8d39?","choice1":"school fee","choice2":"interesting","choice3":"seafood","choice4":"atmosphere","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e2d\u6bd2?","choice1":"be surprised","choice2":"condition, term","choice3":"if","choice4":"to be poisoned, poisoning","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9002\u5e94?","choice1":"toward evening, at dusk, at night fall","choice2":"Means","choice3":"to adapt; to accommodate","choice4":"mention","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u90e8\u5206?","choice1":"price","choice2":"section","choice3":"to go to school","choice4":"again, once more","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0a\u91cd?","choice1":"as, to act as, for (the sake of), to be, to do","choice2":"safe","choice3":"to esteem, to respect, to honor, eminent, serious","choice4":"to hold","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u52a0\u6cb9\u7ad9?","choice1":"GAS","choice2":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","choice3":"price","choice4":"Only","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u767b\u673a\u724c?","choice1":"to oppose","choice2":"a short while, temporary","choice3":"random","choice4":"boarding pass","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7406\u53d1?","choice1":"to bear with, endure","choice2":"to regret","choice3":"taste","choice4":"Haircut","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u54cd?","choice1":"child","choice2":"to ring, to sound","choice3":"opinion","choice4":"print","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5373\u4f7f?","choice1":"even if","choice2":"household, family","choice3":"ancient time","choice4":"Candidates","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6253\u5370?","choice1":"By the way","choice2":"in contrast","choice3":"print","choice4":"task","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6696\u548c?","choice1":"to promote, to sell","choice2":"accurate, exact, precise","choice3":"reporter","choice4":"warm","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0d\u540c?","choice1":"as much as possible","choice2":"difference","choice3":"The Great Wall","choice4":"punctual, on schedule","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5bf9\u9762?","choice1":"at all times, any time","choice2":"opposite","choice3":"disaster","choice4":"a person who goes to bed late,night owl","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7533\u8bf7?","choice1":"From","choice2":"to apply","choice3":"Festival","choice4":"to obtain, to get","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u798f\u5229?","choice1":"welfare","choice2":"international","choice3":"The Great Wall","choice4":"opinion","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u503c\u5f97?","choice1":"the Internet","choice2":"Young man","choice3":"be worth","choice4":"part of it","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51c6\u786e?","choice1":"accurate, exact, precise","choice2":"to come up with, raise , propose","choice3":"full","choice4":"knock","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e00\u65f6?","choice1":"responsibility","choice2":"a short while, temporary","choice3":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","choice4":"in the end","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4ef2\u4ecb?","choice1":"scientist","choice2":"unusal , abnormal","choice3":"agent","choice4":"sweat","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7834?","choice1":"shy, embarrassed","choice2":"broken","choice3":"Off","choice4":"finally","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65e2\u7136?","choice1":"trash can","choice2":"bottom","choice3":"since","choice4":"rent","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u508d\u665a?","choice1":"round trip","choice2":"dirty","choice3":"society","choice4":"toward evening, at dusk, at night fall","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6b63\u786e?","choice1":"annoying","choice2":"correct","choice3":"fruit juice","choice4":"if","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u656c\u9152?","choice1":"to enjoy, to appreciate","choice2":"lazy","choice3":"to toast, to propose a toast","choice4":"confidence","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u73ed?","choice1":"Regardless of","choice2":"mirror","choice3":"invention\/ to invent","choice4":"flight (measure word)","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6708\u521d?","choice1":"to get married","choice2":"early in the month","choice3":"to apply","choice4":"but","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6bb5\uff08\u91cf\u8bcd\uff09?","choice1":"period of","choice2":"purpose","choice3":"happiness","choice4":"to accept","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0f\u4f19\u5b50?","choice1":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","choice2":"scientist","choice3":"Young man","choice4":"loan","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u822a\u73ed?","choice1":"flight","choice2":"bridge","choice3":"action","choice4":"at one\u2019s side, on hand","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u73b0\u91d1?","choice1":"to pull off","choice2":"cash","choice3":"difference","choice4":"travel","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f18\u79c0?","choice1":"credit card","choice2":"customer","choice3":"excellent, outstanding","choice4":"one-time","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u54bd\u5589?","choice1":"to sense, to feel, a feeling, an experience","choice2":"throat","choice3":"to contact","choice4":"pressure","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7fa1\u6155?","choice1":"destination","choice2":"envy, admire","choice3":"international","choice4":"rent","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4eb2\u621a?","choice1":"detailed","choice2":"a short while, temporary","choice3":"beautiful","choice4":"relatives","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u813e\u6c14?","choice1":"and, also","choice2":"print","choice3":"temper","choice4":"to force (sb to do sth","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u514d\u8d39?","choice1":"father","choice2":"free","choice3":"regardless","choice4":"Fiction","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u964d\u4f4e?","choice1":"reduce","choice2":"to hunt","choice3":"to take off","choice4":"sunlight","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e50\u8da3?","choice1":"father","choice2":"admittedly (it's true that...)\u200b","choice3":"joy, fun","choice4":"to understand, to comprehend","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u540c\u65f6?","choice1":"seafood","choice2":"Simultaneously","choice3":"pocket money","choice4":"parking space","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u753b\u5bb6?","choice1":"invention\/ to invent","choice2":"painter","choice3":"disaster","choice4":"to play the host, to host sb","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u539f\u56e0?","choice1":"From","choice2":"careful","choice3":"need","choice4":"reason","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8d39\u7528?","choice1":"master, host, owner","choice2":"between","choice3":"fee, cost","choice4":"money given for children as a New Year\u2019s present","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u538b\u5c81\u94b1?","choice1":"to hunt","choice2":"to allow","choice3":"sure","choice4":"money given for children as a New Year\u2019s present","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6536?","choice1":"customer","choice2":"second","choice3":"Close","choice4":"common","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53e4\u4ee3?","choice1":"copy","choice2":"grape","choice3":"show","choice4":"ancient time","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0f\u9547?","choice1":"to apply","choice2":"panda","choice3":"From","choice4":"town","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6539\u53d8?","choice1":"rich","choice2":"to change, to alter","choice3":"often, frequently","choice4":"to get married","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9a6c\u864e?","choice1":"careless","choice2":"vacation","choice3":"towel","choice4":"hold","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b58?","choice1":"humor","choice2":"Save","choice3":"to approach, to get close to","choice4":"unusal , abnormal","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5374?","choice1":"play piano","choice2":"to allow","choice3":"ancient time","choice4":"but","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u62a5\u5bfc?","choice1":"Author","choice2":"report","choice3":"direction","choice4":"authentic, genuine, local","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6865?","choice1":"at all times, any time","choice2":"again, once more","choice3":"sunlight","choice4":"bridge","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u505c\u8f66\u4f4d?","choice1":"to support","choice2":"living room","choice3":"Inside","choice4":"parking space","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f80\u8fd4?","choice1":"turn","choice2":"round trip","choice3":"to spend","choice4":"citizen","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e3e\u529e?","choice1":"Organized","choice2":"procedure","choice3":"custom, convention","choice4":"taste","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e4b?","choice1":"It","choice2":"dirty","choice3":"Sichuan, a province in southwest China","choice4":"annual leave","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7bc7?","choice1":"cherish","choice2":"Articles","choice3":"Only","choice4":"joke","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53d1\u660e?","choice1":"invention\/ to invent","choice2":"to rent","choice3":"Articles","choice4":"mention","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8868\u793a?","choice1":"bun","choice2":"master","choice3":"to express, to show, to say, to state, to indicate, to mean","choice4":"to represent","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8868\u626c?","choice1":"smokes","choice2":"not only\/have to","choice3":"flight (measure word)","choice4":"to praise, to commend","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5b8c\u5168?","choice1":"tiger","choice2":"completely","choice3":"street","choice4":"authentic, genuine, local","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8981\u662f?","choice1":"happiness","choice2":"if","choice3":"Valentine's Day","choice4":"common","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65b0\u5e74?","choice1":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice2":"how fraction being said in Chinese","choice3":"to understand, to comprehend","choice4":"New Year","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8131?","choice1":"to sense, to feel, a feeling, an experience","choice2":"rush hour,peak time","choice3":"washing machine","choice4":"Off","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f5c\u5bb6?","choice1":"Hold","choice2":"writer","choice3":"to put off, to postpone, to delay","choice4":"explanation, to explain","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6837\u5b50?","choice1":"Looks like","choice2":"one\u2019s thoughts and feelings","choice3":"regular pattern","choice4":"GAS","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u987e\u5ba2?","choice1":"customer","choice2":"Festival","choice3":"random","choice4":"originally","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53ef\u6015?","choice1":"all","choice2":"horrible","choice3":"excellent, outstanding","choice4":"Author","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5ea7?","choice1":"Simultaneously","choice2":"typhoon","choice3":"when the time comes, at that time","choice4":"seat","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u76ee\u7684?","choice1":"E.g","choice2":"purpose","choice3":"master, host, owner","choice4":"Words","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6572?","choice1":"master","choice2":"condition, term","choice3":"to celebrate","choice4":"knock","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u51fa\u751f?","choice1":"Hold","choice2":"direction","choice3":"finally","choice4":"to be born","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u53ea?","choice1":"Inside","choice2":"Measure word for animals (general)","choice3":"vegetarian","choice4":"to compensate","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u957f\u6c5f?","choice1":"wake","choice2":"show","choice3":"a person who goes to bed late,night owl","choice4":"Yangtze","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9633\u53f0?","choice1":"versus","choice2":"balcony","choice3":"early in the month","choice4":"society","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u73af\u4fdd?","choice1":"to pull off","choice2":"Cool","choice3":"to pick","choice4":"environmental protection","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u589e\u52a0?","choice1":"to pull off","choice2":"Festival","choice3":"one way, one path","choice4":"increase","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65e5\u8bb0?","choice1":"diary","choice2":"polite, courteous, modest","choice3":"medical","choice4":"thanks, grateful, thankful","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u63d0?","choice1":"Is it","choice2":"Close","choice3":"appear","choice4":"mention","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8868\u60c5?","choice1":"need","choice2":"middle age person","choice3":"to express, expression, facial expression","choice4":"then","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u80af\u5b9a?","choice1":"whether","choice2":"scientist","choice3":"sure","choice4":"furniture","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u9910\u5177?","choice1":"independent","choice2":"tableware","choice3":"as long as","choice4":"partner, boyfriend, girlfriend,person","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4fe9?","choice1":"both","choice2":"countryside","choice3":"Language","choice4":"All","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f53\u65f6?","choice1":"at that time, while","choice2":"gradually","choice3":"by","choice4":"to pick","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6d6a\u6f2b?","choice1":"business","choice2":"romantic","choice3":"to support","choice4":"to joke","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65e0\u8bba?","choice1":"Exactly","choice2":"international","choice3":"regardless","choice4":"cherish","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5f00\u73a9\u7b11?","choice1":"opposite","choice2":"to joke","choice3":"to attach importance to sth, to value","choice4":"Give","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u54b1\u4eec?","choice1":"shy, embarrassed","choice2":"at the minimum, at the very least","choice3":"we","choice4":"Row","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e60\u60ef?","choice1":"didn't expect","choice2":"habit,get used to","choice3":"sunlight","choice4":"to hold","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6f14\u5458?","choice1":"actor","choice2":"to accept","choice3":"horse","choice4":"measure word for document, paper, portion, part","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u7ecf\u6d4e?","choice1":"WC","choice2":"local","choice3":"flavor","choice4":"economic","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8461\u8404?","choice1":"child","choice2":"results, conclusion, as a result, in the end","choice3":"grape","choice4":"information","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u5c0a\u656c?","choice1":"fax","choice2":"politeness","choice3":"pack","choice4":"to respect, to revere","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u516c\u91cc?","choice1":"Km","choice2":"to pay","choice3":"annoying","choice4":"buffet","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u82b1\u9500?","choice1":"such as","choice2":"relatives","choice3":"expenses,costs","choice4":"strength","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4e0d\u4ec5?","choice1":"specialized, customized","choice2":"to push out, to release","choice3":"atmosphere","choice4":"not only","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of \u65e9\u665a?","choice1":"(used in exclamations )to what an extant","choice2":"summer holiday","choice3":"sooner or later","choice4":"area","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8001\u864e?","choice1":"tiger","choice2":"custom, convention","choice3":"copy","choice4":"loan","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u8f93?","choice1":"lose","choice2":"information","choice3":"and","choice4":"gradually","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of \u4f7f?","choice1":"the best","choice2":"Make","choice3":"when the time comes, at that time","choice4":"parking space","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of \u6761\u4ef6?","choice1":"condition, term","choice2":"Fiction","choice3":"envy, admire","choice4":"skin","answer":1}]